sourcinggate.com 2011-10-15

# Wholesale - China wholesale - Professional Chinese wholesaler - Dropship from China

Collection of information 

When you visit SourcingGate.com, we do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. For instance, we do require registration for the newsletter. If you decide to register for the newsletter, or if you request information from us, you will be asked to provide certain information and details, including your name, country and e-mail address. SourcingGate.com respects your privacy 

We will not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information about our users to other parties, without our users' consent. 

We do, however, share certain aggregate information about our users to our suppliers, i.e. XX% of site visitors is from North America. This enables us to constantly build a large database of products and suppliers, giving you wider shopping options. 

We also reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases. For example, when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally), our title, rights, interests or property, or those of other web site users, or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement, or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority. 

Use of information 

We may use the information you provide to respond to your requests for additional information, to contact you, if necessary, to service your account or for other administrative purposes. We may also access your information to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to enforce agreements between us, or for marketing purposes. In addition, for certain transactions, our system may use your transaction details to automate and to streamline your transaction by checking for electronic data compliance, providing reporting features, and transferring data from previous forms to those of the current transaction. 

We may also use the information you provide for certain mailing initiatives. For example, you may sometimes receive an invitation to answer surveys or try out new products and services from SourcingGate.com.com. Your feedback helps us develop new products and services based on your needs. 

You always have a choice about receiving mailings, surveys or information about products and services from us. Each e-mail you receive has an "Unsubscribe" option. As a registered member, you can also advise us which types of e-mail you wish to receive by updating your Notifications page. 

Can I Correct Or Remove Information on SourcingGate.com?

You always have the option to view your account to make sure the information we have collected from you is indeed correct. You also have the option of removing any information from your account that you wish to keep private. However, please note that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to effectively provide the service or products you have requested. We recommend, that you contact us first to discuss which information you may remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you. 

Changes of Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented. We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes. Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally. You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate.
